{
    "subject": "resource/Dari_(Italian_band)",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "Aosta, Italy",
    "human_readable": "The origin of Dari (Italian band) is Aosta, Italy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8871161937713623,
            "question": "Is Dari an Italian band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8300235271453857,
            "question": "Where is the Italian band Dari from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6613941788673401,
            "question": "What country is Aosta, Italy in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.65800940990448,
            "question": "In which city did Dari originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47322261333465576,
            "question": "Are there any famous bands from Aosta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42723122239112854,
            "question": "What is the musical style of Dari?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35283440351486206,
            "question": "Where would you find the band Dari performing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3341759443283081,
            "question": "What is the origin of the band's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22643160820007324,
            "question": "Has Dari released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12948541343212128,
            "question": "Do they play any other genres besides Italian music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The origin of Dari (Italian band) is Aosta, Italy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2178_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Dari released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2178_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin of the band's name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2178_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you find the band Dari performing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2178_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2178_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the text, dARI is a band from Aosta, Italy that plays electro pop-punk music. This statement is mentioned multiple times throughout the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"dARI is a band from Aosta, Italy,\" which supports the statement that the origin of Dari (the Italian band) is Aosta, Italy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}